hello everybody today is possibly the
most important episode of hermitcraft
that i have ever done i know we haven't
been doing hempcraft for so long but
it's happened my secret project project
dirt house up there
is finished absolutely complete
and instead of just showing you it i
think what i'm gonna do is head straight
over to mumbo's place and pick him up
and bring him over
because
this is this is the biggest thing that
i've ever done
all right here we go
i'm so excited i'm gonna desperately try
to keep it a secret mumbo has no idea
what he's getting into but he knows that
there's been a secret project there for
a while we just gotta find him mumbo
hello hello
it's nice to see you you always make a
very dramatic entrance when you come
over to my base you know that of course
i'll take a bow or take a bow you
haven't been checking your mail what's
going on here
um well yeah you see my mailbox seems to
be filled
right
for some bizarre reason uh i can't quite
seem to work it out but
so the thing that's funny about this
is that i feel like so poultry man has
obviously sent through a lot of eggs huh
right and he's poultry man
poultry man but there also seems to be a
lot of eggs from the chickens that were
also sent through
from poultryman i mean i've just got a
full-blown egg farm working down at this
part of my base now
well might as well take these away from
you oh oh wow there's a backlog going on
oh my god
they're still blowing in
and there's chickens galore out here as
well there's chicken there's chicken in
a boat there's chickens out here uh a
lot of my storage system also has eggs
just constantly being pushed through it
because of all the chickens on top of my
face
hmm
i mean yeah it's um
yeah there's a bit of a poultry vibe
going on with my base right now i think
anyway
what i'm here for is i need to show you
something you're aware right that i've
been working on a project in my base
yeah yeah yeah yeah we discussed our
last meeting yeah well
it's finished i'm like
a few weeks away from you know that
meeting but it's done it works yep
do you want to see it
i'm i'm very curious to know exactly
what it is
so yes yeah 100 it's a show not tell
let's go
okay so this is the bottom layer of my
base nothing's really changed here the
secret project is actually up there on
the first layer
right okay
so this elevator is going to take us up
to the first layer but you haven't
actually done the redstone yet that i
asked you in the last meeting yeah
yeah you know okay
there's a few things on my to-do list
right i'm quite a busy busy guy um and
this is definitely falling by the
wayside that's okay it's not obvious
i don't think
no it shouldn't necessarily be too
difficult but you know i was doing your
beacon project and then you want me to
do a mob farm you know i've got all
sorts of things that i need to work on
designing and yeah and you're doing lots
of commercials for people or adverts
yeah i'm doing yeah the the filming
store has now opened and it turns out
it's actually quite popular people
actually want commercials made for their
shops well we might want a commercial
made for what we've got up there as well
hmm that could be interesting well you
know i'm gonna have to see what it is
yeah come on i'll show you
are you ready i
am my eyes ready um
is this gonna blow me away it walk in
backwards
um okay
[Music]
oh
my goodness it's here
this is it
this is my secret project that i've been
working on
[Laughter]
does it resemble anybody
i mean sort of
i mean ish
oh this is
yeah i mean it it looks it looks quite
he's very
how do i say this handsome he's a bit
goofy handsome
goofy handsome i guess would be the way
that i would describe
what what he's currently looking like
right now i like that i like the tubes
oh they're cool it's you this is you
this is my super computer this is
project dirt house
and that was just that was its secret
code name so now it it honestly needs a
new name
right and yeah this is this is my secret
project that i've been working on it it
is
it is going to do something absolutely
magnificent
i'm very curious and also kind of
terrified as to what that could
potentially entail
i am
i mean where how does it what
what do we even do with it well
the idea is this is like a test run that
we're going to do together because this
is an architect project if you turn
around i've made like a little logo
um i don't know if that's like i don't
know i it was just a prototype idea for
that one so like this is the arc very
cool product
this is a test run so the idea is this
is a money-making scheme
so i i feel like everyone on the server
is going to want to use this machine and
so the idea is you pop your money in
here and it's going to cost
three stacks of diamonds three
three stacks
hang on
it's
it has to do something very special it's
gonna cost you
do you think that's too cheap okay five
stacks
no no no no no no what i'm saying is is
that three that's
that's a lot of diamonds man i've spent
i spent months on this
yeah yeah
but
uh
well okay okay we'll wait and see what
it does
and that's not me saying that i'm not
impressed okay i'm just saying that
three stacks of diamonds is a lot it's a
lot of diamonds you know i think that's
more than i own so
yeah i'm hoping this will make me from a
poor man to a rich man
yeah it sounds like it okay
are we are we ready
i mean i'm so scared and i don't even
really know what it does
i want you to stand back okay i'm gonna
press the button i want you to stand
back and and look at the whole thing
and i'm gonna join okay
are you are you ready
i am i'm terrified but yes okay
three
two
one
[Applause]
[Laughter]
but wait what does it what is that all
that it does oh yeah that's all that it
does but hopefully if it's worked mumbo
this should be more than just a
beautiful specter of removing a mustache
from a machine
because it works
[Laughter]
it removes
your mustache i have officially done it
i have taken your mustache away
dude
the only the only problem is i don't
know where it puts the mustache once
it's taking it away
look at yourself
what
look look at this we've got a mustache
up to your eyes you haven't messed up
your eyes well maybe maybe you should
gross a smaller mustache
how could you not feel that that feels
like it would really hurt it's
painless absolutely painless i feel like
now we're going to make lots of money
oh my word
i i don't know if it's
you know this is like that awful
situation where you know when someone
dyes their hair black or but they leave
their eyebrows and it's just blatantly
obvious you kind of have a crazy
situation
i i feel like i look majorly like a
villain now
i don't know what you look like dude
wait a minute take off your take off
your helmet for the full effect
oh my god well i'm glad that the hair on
top stayed i suppose yeah it doesn't
take much just the mustache it's just
the mustache oh my god like you look
oddly i look like voldemort yeah you
really don't look good i'm sorry
yeah
it's not a good look for me it's not a
goddess
i think i'd be the first to agree you're
like santa claus with no hair
hold on can we stand side by side for a
second
i can't believe that this worked
now here's the thing i designed this
machine to take your mustache away the
thing that i've been threatening to do
since the very first few episodes of
hermitcraft and i finally did it but the
thing is i designed this machine to
translocate your mustache somewhere on
the server right so it happened to go on
me now
but maybe if we try it again it'll go
somewhere else
more but before we do anything i mean
how do i get my mustache back is there
any way to get my mustache back have you
thought this far ahead grin
no
didn't i didn't make a moustache
retrieval machine
do you know how long it takes me to grow
this mustache dude i'm not one of those
guys that can grow a mustache overnight
this took me that takes me months
uh i'm sure we can figure it out i'm
sure if like i'm sure if i just return
it
yeah yeah just return it i'll get a pair
of shears and put it back
maybe run at each other really fast and
just move the transfers over
come on let's do it
all right i mean we can give it a whirl
are you ready let's see if this works
three i think i'm ready two
one charge
painless again painless did it work
looks like the
looking good it's back where it belongs
man that i'm surprised that that didn't
hurt because that feels like that would
be an incredibly painful process yeah
dude i don't even imagine is your
mustache like part of you or is it it's
like a caterpillar it can just be
just peeled off and put somewhere is it
real is it like a sticker
yeah yeah that's actually that's the the
great secret it's actually like a toupee
mustache
a moustache toupee the main downfall of
this machine is that i've i've now got
to manually reset it
okay right okay yeah sorry i'll just
give me two seconds to tinker with this
and it is back to normal i'm not clever
enough to make it so that it just auto
resets but it works um
yeah he's got we've got the mustache
back on the screen it feels like yeah my
mustache is still still on my face yep
and i factored this into the cast you
see because it takes such a long time to
reset the machine that's why it's so
expensive as well like my time has to be
factored into this
right yeah your diamond hourly rate
exactly which happens to be two and a
half stacks of diamonds
expensive expensive services right there
mustache mustache removal and
replacement as well
one heck of a barber but do you agree
with me that you think that every hermit
on the server is gonna want a piece of
your mustache
yeah no i think i can agree this is a
coveted mustache it's a it's an
award-winning mustache and
the way in which it is removed and
replaced is is quite something it's it's
quite the spectacle so yeah i can
imagine that a lot of people are going
to want a piece of this and also some
people on this server have more money
than cents so
yeah we want those those are the ones
we're targeting this is a redistribution
scheme that's what this is
[Laughter]
exactly all right shall i
shall i pull the lever again
uh don't pull the lever because we don't
know what that does just yet yeah it
might replace another type of hair and i
don't i don't want to see what no
knowing my redstone these things just
explode everything so
i'll stick with the button here we go
three all right
two
one uh
i get so nervous when i see this thing
starting
the music's a great touch
i'm gonna take that
away
[Applause]
it never gets boring
oh every time oh that's beautiful has it
but has it worked
i mean
yep oh yeah it's
it's worked it's gone again
is it is it on me it's no it's not new
what
hang on lift up take your elite off okay
i want to see yeah it might be on my
back somewhere
oh you're wearing something
hold on let me check no it's definitely
not up there i can see that it's not on
the back of my head
no no it's not on the top of your head
lift up your feet
is there any way that you can lift up
your feet
don't take it hold on
check the bottom of my soles is your
mustache on my feet
no you've got no no um
all right is it on that iron golem
that would be impressive if it was
but no it doesn't
wait
well that's what this machine does it
does take your mustache away
and part of the fun is finding it do you
want to go and have a quick look for it
i mean like i guess i haven't is there a
radius that this thing operates or is
this well i would ask if you're attached
to your mustache but you're clearly not
yeah um
so so you're telling me that it could be
anywhere oh yeah absolutely anywhere the
middle of nowhere the middle of
somewhere
on someone's face it could be anywhere
hmm i don't know why i agree to do the
things that you tell me to do like this
because we like diamonds mumbo this is
this is what architects are all about
it's very true right so should we go on
it yeah
i'm gonna make it very quick
oh i forgot to put my headlight back on
wait did you just just go straight to
the floor
yes
nice okay
i've only done that more than two times
i was gonna say yeah how many how many
times have you done that
all right uh i've made it day where are
you at
i'm up at the top where the pros end up
the ones who remember to pit there did
you see that did you see how swish my
flying was that looking how swish that
looks so good you have no idea
all right
i guess the best place to look is the
shopping district
yeah yeah let's fly over there maybe we
can check impulses maybe we can check
impulse's face and jevin's face if
they're about see if we can all right
okay how about this all right place your
bets
impulse
no it's not on tango or cubs face no
it's not on the statue of hermity
no
it's i mean my my pumpkin face has a
mustache
but i think that was already there yeah
i mean this is going to be a problem
because there's plenty of bumbos around
and we have to how do we distinguish
between the two no yeah it's a good
question did your mum sew like a label
in the back of your mustache to like
your name
i mean well so
i mean i've never noticed it i might
have i you know when i was born because
obviously i was born with a mustache oh
yeah maybe my mum might have sewn one in
just in case i misplaced it exactly she
foresaw this mums are so good like that
yeah yeah yeah uh
no i don't see it i wonder do you know
where anyone lives because i don't know
where impulse or jevin lives
no
i'm a terrible hermit all right
uh this is we both oh wait is that him
no that's his horse don't tell him i
said that
oh my gosh
that's so rude i just saw some diamond
armor okay he's just gone anyway all
right we can rule out jevin
i don't know where impulse is basically
well we can see him in the tab menu i
suppose and he doesn't look like him or
his camera have a mustache that's true
it could have been on the back of his
head or something but i don't know oh
that's true dude i don't know where this
is
well
so
should we just
chill for a bit yeah i guess i don't
there's nothing we can do if your
mustache isn't here maybe it takes a
little while to translocate
i don't know
it was pretty instant for us you built
the machine man and you're telling me
you don't know it's
10 parts magic
10 parts madness and a whole lot of
science okay i don't know how it works
exactly
what are even the ratios there
did you miss the part where we had
madness in it
yeah okay okay i get you know what else
is madness oh my goodness come over here
i'm by the statue of hermity
you look so silly
i'm aware all right okay i'm aware that
i look like a four-year-old at this
point in time a four-year-old in his
dad's suit okay i know do you know
yeah yeah yeah doc was explaining this
to me the other day he never actually
explained how you do it wait it's
possible to how do you do this
he said it's using some piston trickery
huh
but doc has also this is a this is a
crazy killing machine this is a this is
a machine that charges up an anvil then
fires it at you and you just die
instantly
you can only use it what
oh there's a chance but
i hope we haven't broken anything for
the kill tanker challenge
oh my goodness
i couldn't help myself dude if you put a
big red button in front of me and say do
not press this button i will press the
button
did you hear the urgency of my voice yes
i was really scared
oh my word well so we have we've done
nothing but break things and not found a
mustache
so um great
uh i guess i've got things to do at my
base so i guess we'll
find it another day
yeah you're just going to leave me out
to dry like this you're just going to
leave me out of dry think of all the
diamonds stacks and stacks of diamonds
it's true
it's true i can buy an upper lip warmer
with all the diamonds
by a lip scarf
exactly
all right well i'll speak to you later
then all right bye
now that mumbo's gone i think we should
probably get on with some actual work
now so i think what i'm gonna do is
i had some really good feedback on what
the towers should look like now it was
pretty 50 50 about keeping it like this
or
changing it up
so i don't know what to do but everyone
said the stripes look good even if they
did look like a specific logo but don't
worry i'm pretty sure when i add
multiple ones in it won't look that bad
at all and another suggestion was
instead of using the
dark
the darker version of concrete to use
this which matches what i've got going
on here so i'm going to give that a go
as well but the other thing is i'm not
gonna just add some stripes in here i'm
not gonna add just the three stripes i
think what i'm gonna try and do today
without actually prototyping it it's
adding in an indent here or something or
maybe maybe even here oh this is still
even powder i should probably get a
bucket of water
i wonder if i can do this entire thing
flying
so all i gotta do is go up here
ow
oh nailed it
and then place some water
and that should do the trick
and if i'm quick
this yep there we go all of that
concrete powder i think there's actually
quite a few spots just like this where i
really needed to put in
water here earlier but i didn't
and hopefully that will just slowly make
its way down
and now i need to just work out where
this indent is gonna go because the
stripes are gonna go down here so maybe
a small indent um here maybe it's gonna
be incredibly difficult to make this
look right because the stripe or maybe i
could do one on that side and one on
this side
i don't really know well one two maybe i
should just do the stripes first
[Music]
if only i can remember exactly where
they started
oh
i think we should probably start fairly
high up
and the other thing that's gonna come
into play here
is that i want to use the inside of
these towers as a mob farm
so that could be a slight problem in the
future
but for now well i i will need to take
out all of these gubbins in the middle
so i'm not too worried but for now i'm
sure we can just make do with what we've
got
we should probably take a little step
back before we commit to this just to
make sure that it's at the right height
yeah i'm pretty sure that will work it
looks so odd like that
there we go that's one done i think i
don't know whether to take this down a
notch into the inside but i might just
leave that fairly clean for now so it
goes three along and then one down three
along one down and that should give us
our nice diagonal then i've just got to
replicate that over
all the way around so this could end up
being quite a time consuming task
but i think this will make the base look
really nice
that's one stripe complete let's take a
little step back and see what that looks
like
not too shabby that doesn't look too bad
at all and i think with that diagonal in
that specific angle what if i just did
one on each
just a brainwave what if i did one on
each one
that could look even better than just
three there and that might give me more
space to do different details
let's give that one a go as well i need
to make sure that they're probably the
same distance away
building while flying is definitely not
easy especially as most of the time you
just gotta plant into the wall to make
sure you get some scaffolding
so if i can count correctly which i
normally can't
one two three four five six seven so
that's the top block
so we'll be able to tell if the stripes
on multiple layers works as soon as
we've built a couple more of them
the only thing is if they don't work i
can just cover it up using the white
concrete only i don't have to worry
about like putting the terracotta back
in my hands it doesn't really matter too
much now normally i would time lapse
this kind of thing but today i thought i
would just do it and show you kind of
what my thought process is while i'm
building because this one this
particular build
is
semi-planned and inspired but then it
just went totally free form the towers
were a planned idea but not the way i
executed it at all so
it's very interesting how this is coming
together indeed i also feel like i need
a new project to work on because i'm
always constantly working on my base in
the background that's kind of become
normal but i need something else to
occupy my time something funny i feel
like an architect thing in each layer
would be really fun
but i'm not entirely sure
i think that'll do it for this one i
have not checked that that's correct at
all but we'll take a little look and see
[Music]
that doesn't look too bad
let's take another look
that actually looks pretty decent i
would say i might have to stop them
short because this gets progressively
thinner but it could look really good
another one there and another one up
there would look really rad i think and
then that would leave me a big chunk to
work with here for a completely separate
kind of detail but this particular angle
isn't matched anywhere else on the build
so it kind of stands out a little bit
weird but i think i could work with it i
really do
it needs something these towers are too
plain i've said it time and time again
they just need something but i don't
want to overthink anything too much on
this build i just want to go with my gut
my gut is telling me many many stripes
time for a third little look at what
we're doing here
and it doesn't quite look right well
it's not all the way filled in but you
can see where it stops
something's not right there so these two
work well because they stop at the glass
and just end there and it looks like
it's all nicely connected
but this one makes it look
just
wrong hmm
i might come back to this another time
because i sometimes it's nice to make
little bits of progress and instead
especially when you don't know what
you're doing with a build sometimes it
can be incredibly wrong to go with
something where you're winging it and
then come back to it and decide that's
not what you want at all
so i think what i'm going to do is leave
the work on the build for today
and maybe experiment a bit more in
creative
that way i can i don't know i can come
up with a few more ideas before
committing to one thing
now because i've been so busy working on
the base i haven't actually had time to
go and check any of my shops
so
i've just i'm so easily distracted
let's go and see if we've got any
diamonds to collect i should really
restart oh yeah we sold all of the
quartz as usual
and we've sold all of the sand as well
oh my goodness
21 diamonds not bad gravel is actually
pretty valuable for me at the moment i
might shift some of this back especially
if i'm making a lot of changes to my
base i'll leave a little bit but 21
diamonds is not bad i wonder if the
pickle shop sold anything
uh
mumbo just said grian i found it i've
asked him where where did he find it
guardian farm
apparently he's found it at the guardian
farm is it it's scowls or x's so the
mustache has been found i knew it would
be somewhere let's quickly check the
pickle shop and then go and join mumbo
no
to be honest i think cub cleared me out
of pickles a while ago because i checked
and there was like 20 diamonds worth so
no pickle sales today not very often
that people need a load of pickles i'll
pop those in there let's go and let's go
and see about this mustache i'm i'm
really interested to see what's happened
to it well we made loads of diamonds and
we've been pretty busy with the base
and we found mumbo's mustache i'm pretty
sure once we open up the mustache shop
well it needs a name this machine it
needs a name i need like an anagram of
mumbo or something like or stash or
something like that i need a really cool
anagram to use for this machine and like
then we can do like an advert for it and
see what happens there because i'm
fairly sure that everyone on this server
is genuinely going to want to use it
just for fun
because it's rather an inconvenience to
mumbo he's not complete without his
mustache all right we're at the we're at
the guardian farm now
uh it's clearly not above here unless we
take a look down
well there's all the guardians oh my
goodness
that's a lot of guardians i've never
really appreciated this before but that
is madness
um he must be inside
is he down oh there he is you're right
yeah so where is it i
you know it's it's big
i wasn't expecting this
i know is this it's a it's a it's a
translocator of of the mustache but also
a transsizer
yeah that's not the same mustache that
was on the machine i would know it's a
stylist as well yeah i i mean i made the
machine so this
this is not exactly the same mustache so
does that mean it could also get smaller
um i i mean
i don't know you keep asking me
questions as if i know the answer to
dude it's your machine dude you built
this thing
magic dude don't don't need to explain
magic okay um yeah
do we just remove it then
i think we just take it that i mean
it'd be wrong with us to just leave it
up here well yeah but i feel how do we
get this back on your face just wait
hold on go and face plant it see if that
works
yeah that worked last time
but i feel like if this ends up on my
face then
i'm not going to be able to fit through
doors anymore
that would be hilarious no go on give it
a go give it a go
hang on i'll take my helmet off hang on
hang on hang on i'll take my helmet off
it might have been the head protection
yeah yeah go on
no nothing done
it just hurt
not working
hmm so
do we shave how many times in this
episode are you gonna stress me out dude
sorry i'm
i'm i'm just so excited
i mean do we take it down i if we take
it down will my mustache be lost forever
is it that sort of deal uh
hmm i don't know
i'm just
i'm just gonna use logic here let's
let's take it down and we'll scoop up
the individual hairs
yeah
oh hold on there's a there's a sign
behind it
there's a sign
mambo's mustache if dude your mum did
come on mum
it's good to see you good to see that
she's taking care of me all right okay
well that's that's that do we include
the sign as well i guess the sign has to
come with it okay uh oh you missed a
block don't can't miss a single hair
right give them give them more to me
give them all to me we need to keep them
together
okay
all right
so 43 blocks of black concrete and a
sign
um yep
i i honestly thought
that hold on maybe if i just give them
all to you your mustache will appear
what that
hmm
has it worked no
no no um
if you
were to fire them at me
really hard at my face
with what
dispenser
you don't want to kill you don't want to
blow my head off which is like a
dispenser
i made a machine that i don't fully
understand
dispense the blocks onto my head green
otherwise i'm gonna get really upset
okay
do you have a dispenser
no of course i don't have a dispenser i
don't carry dispensers on me all right
should we should we go grab one yeah
let's go grab one
all right
are you coming mumbo
mate i'm i need to repair my nature
all right sweet i'm good to go now was
that it that was so fun
now
should we when should we open up the
machine well first of all we need to
name the machine and i've asked my
audience for some suggestions of like
anagrams or something and then we could
maybe use the best one
yeah but when do we want to open this
machine
um
i don't know i guess i mean that's
entirely once again it is your machine
it's an architect machine it only works
with the both of us
whenever you feel
the world is ready for it okay i have
one dispenser i have one dispenser
all right i've wondered okay all right
i'm i'm set
okay now we do we hook this up to a
redstone clock you're just gonna
i've just got one of these
this is how i do redstone
this is the manual redstone clock it's
very surprising that you managed to
build that machine if if if that's the
sort of redstone is that how it's
powered is that why do you think it took
me so long
right you load it up with the sign and
everything that was in it before
even a single block out of place and it
won't go it won't go back i think right
all right this is the stupidest thing
i've ever seen i think i've done many
stupid things in hermitcraft but i have
never done this all right are you ready
yep okay
and
you're in three
two
one
oh oh my that actually hurts a little
bit man
all right i think it might be like
halfway on
my fingers hurt
i should have done all right the
redstone okay we're good we're good
we're good we're good i think i think
it's all there
is it done
you good
the cup look
yes
on
it's back
that is this is so stupid that is the
stupidest thing i don't know how this
magic works
this is this has been ridiculous so i
think
yeah three stacks of diamonds makes it
worth the
heavy heavy
stress that it puts on the two of us
mainly yeah absolutely um yeah but if if
they're using it too much if the price
is going up i'm telling you
right okay so three stacks of diamonds
when does it open
i don't know i'm gonna i think i'm going
to
i'm gonna reset the machine
and then wait a second or two and then
like maybe we could do an advert for it
or something or we need to promote it in
some way because this is in my base it's
not in the shopping district so yeah
really needs to be something
i think so yeah all right well i you
know i know a guy who who might be just
perfect for that do i really have to pay
you
well no hang on hang on wait you're
telling me i got my my mustache forcibly
removed twice in today's video yeah and
you're and and also i know that you're
getting three stacks of diamonds per use
of this machine
50 50 split okay okay that's fair enough
yeah no no you don't have to pay me at
all i'll make the best commercial ever
would you like to see my mustache
removed
of course you would
it
is going to be exactly like that i can't
wait all right well thank you ever so
much for
for building that ridiculous ridiculous
money-making machine uh first project of
architect is going incredibly well to
think it's been a huge success this all
started because i sang that stupid afk
song i know
and here we are today
and in in a month's time we'll look back
when we're balling out of control in a
yacht outside of monaco thinking it's
all gone well riding riding a giant boat
shaped like a mustache
exactly exactly
all right well thank you so much man i'm
gonna head back to my things now that my
mustache has been fully returned and uh
i look forward to doing more mustache
removals and replacements in the future
yes
now that we've found mumbo's mustache
and it's successfully back on his face i
have reset the machine
and boy oh boy
it is glorious so a lot of you did
successfully guess that this is what i
was working on behind my spoiler wall a
machine or a way to take mumbo's
mustache away now i feel like i should
sing the song but i'm definitely not
going to now this was incredibly
difficult to make not only did i have to
come up with a way to fill this space
very nice and neatly with all of the
different little trinkets i mean there's
like bubbles going up here there's an
iron golem in there there's all sorts of
like fireworks that go off when you
activate it
and yeah this is how we're gonna make
money i'm really excited to see it now
there is a bit of magic going on in the
inside and it was very difficult to make
now i'm not going to show you too much
about what's over my head because that's
where all the magic is to be honest with
you but down here you can see a bunch of
note blocks now i actually had a lot of
help from family craft dad who helped me
put together this song he actually
remixed the mumbo afk song ages ago and
he made a noteblock version so he gave
me everything i needed to know the
spaces the notes
and i managed to replicate it after many
many attempts so thank you very much
family craft dad and it kind of goes
something like this mambo jumbo
[Music]
i might have got a few notes wrong i'm
not sure only family graph i'm pretty
sure family craft dad will tell me if
i've got this wrong
but yeah that's the whole song i'm not
going to activate it because if i
activate it we're going to lose mumbo's
mustache almost immediately anyway let's
get out of here the inner workings of
the mumbo's mustache machine which still
needs an official name i feel is going
to remain somewhat a secret
so yeah i'm so proud of this machine and
i'm hoping that this will give us
infinite amounts of fun on the server so
that's it for me everyone thank you so
much for watching this very very special
episode of minecraft hermitcraft and i
will see you in the next one
i'm definitely going to use this machine
to take his mustache away
all the time
bye